Victory is the only option
War Pigs is a war, action film directed by Ryan Little.
A rag tag unit of misfits known as the War Pigs must go behind enemy
lines to exterminate Nazis by any means necessary.
Captain Jack Wosick, played by Luke Goss.
Captain Hans Picault, played by Dolph Lundgren.
Sergeant McGreevy, played by Chuck Liddell.
August Chambers, played by Noah Segan.
Preacher, played by Steven Luke.
Major A.J. Redding, played by Mickey Rourke.
War Pigs (also released as Saints and Soldiers: War Pigs in the international market), is a 2015 American action
war film directed by Ryan Little, from a script co-written by Luke Schuetzle and Adam Emersonand.
It is the fourth installment in the Saints and Soldiers film series, and
is a standalone sequel to Saints and Soldiers: The Void.
The film stars Luke Goss, Dolph Lundgren, Chuck Liddell, and Mickey Rourke.